Postcards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Postcards, 2.1.7
  - Florence, Italy, circa 1922; 15 (Box 1600)
    - [Palazzo Vecchio], 5
    - Palazzo Vecchio, Firenze, 5-verso
    - La Madonna della Seggiola (nella sua cornice originale) [The Madonna of the Chair (in its original frame)], Firenze, Raffaello Sanzio. Of the chair, Sistine Madonna at Dresden., 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - FIRENZE. Palazzo Pratoria - La Scala; Bargello [inner courtyard], 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - FIRENZE. Ponte Vecchio, 8
    - Florence. Ponte Vecchio. The Ponte Vecchio, or Old Bridge, is said to have existed as early as the Roman period, and was finally rebuilt, after its repeated demolition, by Taddeo Gaddi in 1345. It consists of three arches, over which a covered passage is carried. Its sides are lined with goldsmiths' shops, which have stood there for centuries., 8-verso
    - FIRENZE. Piazza dell'Annunziata e Ospedale degl'Innocent. [Annunziata Square and the Foundling Hospital], 9
    - Piazza dell'Annunziata. At the left corner of this picturesque square is the Palazzo Riccardi-Mannelli, a brick ediface with ornamentation in stone, erected by Buontalenti in 1565. The square is embellished with two baroque fountains; in the background is the Spedale degli Innocenti or Foundinling Hospital., 9-verso
    - Roma, L'Aurora [The Aurora], Guido Reni., 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - [Florence], 11
    - Florence (Italian "Firenze") was formerly the capital of the Grand Duchy of Tuscany; from 1865 to 1870 it was the capital of the kingdom of Italy, and it ranks with Rome, Naples and Venice as one of the most attractive towns in Italy. In the middle ages the fine arts attained here the zenith of their glory, and still to-day an amazing profusion of treasures of art, as well as the delightful environs, render it one of the most beautiful cities in the world., 11-verso
  - Rome, Italy, circa 1922; 16 (Box 1600)
    - EDITORE A DI FRANCESCO D'ATRI, IL CENACOLO- LEONARDO DA VINCI, STAB. A MARZI-ROMA [The Last Supper], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - ROMA Panorama della Citt visto della Cupola di S. Pietro. [Panorama of the city seen from the dome of St. Peter], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - ROMA Basilica di S. Paolo fuori le mura [Basilica of St. Paul outside the walls], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - ROMA Basilica di S. Giovanni in Laterano. [Basilica of Saint John Lateran]; Mother Church, 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - ROMA - Interno della Basilica di S. Paolo [Interior of the St. Paul Basilica], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - Opera la Fosca about this castle, 6
    - Verso: Roma - Castel S. Angelo e S. Pietro, 6-verso
    - EDITORE A DI FRANCESCO D'ATRI, AURORA, G. RENI, STAB. A MARZI-ROMA, 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - [Rome area- The Pyramid of Caius Cestius], 8
    - Roma (dintorni) - La Piramide di Caio Cestio [Rome (vicinity) - The Pyramid of Caius Cestius], 8-verso
    - Roma - Castel Sant'Angelo visto dal Lungotevere [Sant'Angelo Castle seen from the Tiber River], 9
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 9-verso
    - ROMA Scala Santa [The Holy Stairs], 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - [Rome- Via Appia [The Appian Way]- Tomb of Cecilia Metella], 11
    - Roma - Via Appia [The Appian Way] - Tomba di Cecilia Metella, 11-verso
    - Roma - Colonna di Foca; Phocas [The Column of Phocas]- Foro Romano [Roman Forum], 12
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 12-verso
    - Made by Michelangelo - ROMA- Fontan di Trevi. - Trevy Fountain, 13
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 13-verso
    - Roma - Foro Romano [Roman Forum], 14
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 14-verso
    - [Rome - Trinit de Monti; Church of the Santissima Trinita dei Monti & Spanish Steps], 15
    - ROMA - Trinit dei Monti., 15-verso
    - [Rome - Trevi Fountain], 16
    - Rima - Fontana di Trevi, 16-verso
    - Roma - Stanze; Incendio di Borgo [Fire in the Borgo], Raffaello., 17
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 17-verso
    - [Rome- Monument of Victor Emmanuel II], 18
    - Roma - Monumento a Vittorio Emanuele II., 18-verso
    - [Rome- The Pantheon], 19
    - Roma - Il Pantheon., 19-verso
    - Roma - Isola Tiberina [Tiber Island, 20
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 20-verso
    - [Rome- Momentano Bridge], 21
    - Roma - Ponte Momentano, 21-verso
    - Roma - Piazza Venezia col Monumento Vittorio Emanuele II, 22
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 22-verso
    - Roma - Campidoglio [Capitol], 23
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 23-verso
    - ROMA- Basilica di S. Maria Maggiore, 24
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 24-verso
    - Roma - Monumento a Vittorio Emanuele II., 25
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 25-verso
    - ROMA - Tevere e Castel S. Angelo [Tiber River and S. Angelo Castle], 26
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 26-verso
    - ROMA Trinit del Monti - Spanish steps., 27
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 27-verso
    - ROMA - Palazzo del Quirinale - Royal Palace, 28
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 28-verso
  - Rome, Italy, circa 1922; 17 (Box 1600)
    - ROMA Monumento a G. Garibaldi, 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Rome - Pincio - Fountain of Moses], 2
    - Roma - Pincio - Fontana del Mos, 2-verso
    - [Rome - View from the French Academy], 3
    - Roma - Veduta dall'Accademia di Francia. [View from the French Academy], 3-verso
    - [Roman Forum ruins], 4
    - Roma - Foro Romano [Roman Forum], 4-verso
    - [Around Rome - Temple of Vesta with fountain), 5
    - Roma (dintorni) - Tempio di Vesta con Fontana [Rome (vicinity) - Temple of Vesta with fountain], 5-verso
    - Roma - Piramide Caio Cesito con porta S. Paolo; Keals [?] + Schelly; cemetary protestant], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - [Venice - Square of St. Trovaso], 7
    - VENEZIA - Squero S. Trovaso, 7-verso
    - [Rome - Villa Borghese and lake], 8
    - Roma - Villa Borghese - Il Lago., 8-verso
    - [Rome - Arch of Constantine], 9
    - Roma - Arco di Costantino, 9-verso
    - [Rome- Ruins of the Capitol from the Roman Forum], 10
    - Roma - Il Campidoglio dal Foro Romano [The Capitol of the Roman Forum], 10-verso
    - [Rome - St. Peter Plaza], 11
    - Roma - Piazza S. Pietro., 11-verso
    - [Rome - Bridge and Castle of St. Angelo], 12
    - Roma - Ponte e Castel S. Angelo [Bridge and Castle of St. Angelo], 12-verso
    - [Rome - Colosseum], 13
    - Roma - Il Colosseo., 13-verso
    - [Rome - Church of the Santissima Trinita dei Monti & Spanish Steps], 14
    - Roma- Trinit del Monti [and Spanish Steps], 14-verso
    - [Rome - Roman country-side], 15
    - Roma - Campagna Romana, 15-verso
    - [Rome - Tivoli - Villa d'Este; Italian Renaissance Garden], 16
    - Roma - Tivoli - Villa d' Este, 16-verso
    - [Rome - Capitol], 17
    - Roma - Campidoglio [Capitol], 17-verso
    - [Rome - Roman country-side], 18
    - Roma - Campagna Romana. [Roman country-side], 18-verso
    - Roma - Portico dell'Accademia - Casa di Domiziano - Palazzo dei Cesari [Portico of the academy, Palace of Domitian, Palace of the Caesars], 19
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 19-verso
    - ROMA Il Pantheon, 20
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 20-verso
    - Roma - Via Appia Nuova [The new Appian Way], 21
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 21-verso
    - Roma - Via Appia Antica - Tomba di Seneca [Ancient Appian Way - Tomb of Seneca], 22
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 22-verso
    - Roma - Il Colosseo - Interno [Inside of the Colosseum], 23
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 23-verso
    - Roma - Arco di Costantino [Arch of Constantine], 24
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 24-verso
    - ROMA - Il Colosseo o Anfiteatro Flavio [The Colosseum, or Flavian Amphitheater], 25
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 25-verso
    - Roma - Foro Romano del Campidoglio [Roman Capitol], 26
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 26-verso
  - Sicily, Italy, circa 1922; 18 (Box 1600)
    - [Sicilian cart], 1
    - Carretto Siciliano [Sicilian Cart], 1-verso
  Box 1601
- Postcards, 2.1.7
  - Venice, Italy, circa 1922; 1 (Box 1601)
    - "Veduta del Plazzo Ducale di Venezia" [View of the Ducale Plaza in Venice] Canaletto, 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Venezia - Isola di Giorgio], 2
    - Verso: Venezia - 5. Isola di S. Giorgio [Island of St. Giorgio], 2-verso
    - [Venezia - Cancal Grande - Palazzo Franchetti], 3
    - Verso: Venezia - 2. Cancal Grande - Palazzo Franchetti, 3-verso
    - "Veduta del Palazzo Ducale di Venezia" Canaletto, 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - "Il Canal Grande a Venezia e Ponte di Rialto" Canaletto (The Grand Canal and Rialto Bridge in Venice)], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - [Venezia - Rio del Carmine], 6
    - Verso: VENEZIA - Rio del Carmine; Venice, 6-verso
    - [Venezia - Ponte dei Sospiri, The Bridge of Sighs], 7
    - Verso: VENEZIA - Ponte dei Sospiri [The Bridge of Sighs], 7-verso
    - [Venezia - 8. Piazzetta verso S. Giorgio, Plaza towards S. Giorgio], 8
    - Verso: Venezia - 8. Piazzetta verso S. Giorgio, 8-verso
    - [Venezia - 9. Rio di S. Marina], 9
    - Verso: Venezia- 9. Rio di S. Marina, 9-verso
    - [Venezia - Piazza S. Marco e Campanile], 10
    - Verso: VENEZIA - Piazza S. Marco e Campanile, 10-verso
    - [Venezia - 10. Piazzetta S. Marco verso la Salute, S. Marco Square towards the Saint Mary of Health church], 11
    - Verso: Venezia- 10. Piazzetta S. Marco verso la Salute, 11-verso
    - [Venezia - Canal Grande e Chiesa della Salute, Grand Canal and the Saint Mary of Health church], 12
    - Verso: VENEZIA - Canal Grande e Chiesa della Salute, 12-verso
    - [Venezia - Palazzo Ducale, Ducal Palace], 13
    - Verso: VENEZIA - Palazzo Ducale, 13-verso
    - [Venezia -Ponte dei Sospiri, the Bridge of Sighs], 14
    - Verso: VENEZIA -Ponte dei Sospiri, 14-verso
    - [Venezia - Palazzo Ducale, Ducal Palace], 15
    - Verso [Venezia - Palazzo Ducale], 15-verso
    - [Venezia - Palazzo Ca d'Oro ("golden house"); Palazzo Santa Sofia, Saint Sofia Palace], 16
    - Verso: VENEZIA - Palazzo Ca d'Oro, 16-verso
    - [Venezia- Squero S. Trovaso], 17
    - Verso: VENEZIA- Squero S. Trovaso, 17-verso
    - [Venezia - Canal Grande], 18
    - Verso: VENEZIA - Canal Grande, 18-verso
    - [Venezia - Ponte di Rialto, Rialto Bridge], 19
    - Verso: VENEZIA - Ponte di Rialto, 19-verso
  - Malaysia [& Indonesia & Hong Kong], undated; 2 (Box 1601)
    - [Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - [Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - [Buddha at Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - [Staircase archway Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - American Consulate, Penang. S.S., 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - Aberdeen, Hong Kong, 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - [Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 8
    - Verso [Rice, creamed beans, stringed beans, meat, meat balls, chicken, fried eggs, fried fish, pickles, [?] peppers, [?] -toasted ground, chili, crisp bread, squash - green, salad-cucumber, tomato, egg hard boiled, 8-verso
    - [Buddha at Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 9
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 9-verso
    - [Buddha at Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - [Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 11
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 11-verso
    - [Carvings at Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 12
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 12-verso
    - [Carvings at Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 13
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 13-verso
    - [Borobudur, Mahayana Buddhist Temple], 14
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 14-verso
    - Note: Hotel Boroboedoer; Gelegen in de onmiddellijke nabijheid van den Boroboedoer. Schitterende wandelingen. Onvergetelijke natuurgezichten. [Located in the immediate vicinity of the Borobudur. Beautiful walks. Unforgettable nature faces.] Beheerder [Administrator] C.A. NEIJS.], 15
  - The Netherlands, circa 1922; 3 (Box 1601)
    - [Scheveningen; Wandelhoofd [Walking Head]; seaside boardwalk], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Den Haag - Koninklijk Paleis [Royal Palace]], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - [Den Haag. Vredspaleis], 3
    - Verso: Vredespaleis - Den Haag, Palace of Peace - The Hague, Friedenspalast - Haag, Palais de la Paix - La Hague} Holland, 3-verso
    - [Den Haag. Vredespaleis], 4
    - Verso: Vredespaleis - Den Haag, Palace of Peace - The Hague, Friedenspalast - Haag, Palais de la Paix - La Hague} Holland, 4-verso
  - Switzerland, undated; 4 (Box 1601)
    - [1524 Bern. Bundespalast. Palais Federal; federal palace.], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [1545 Bern - Bundespalast mit Kirchenfeldbrucke, Federal Palace and Church Field Bridge], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - [1510 Bern. Kornhausbrucke, Granary Bridge], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - [1544 Bern - Bundespalast, Casino und Kirchenfeldbrucke [Church Field Bridge], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - [1543 Bern und die Alpen (Bern and the Alps); Monch 4105m, Jungfraujoch 3457m, Jungfrau 4166m, Ebnefluh 3964m, Breithorn 3779, Gspaltenhorn 3436m, Blumlisalp 3669m, Doldenhorn 3647m], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - [Interlaken und die Jungfrau, Small town at the base of the Bernese Alps.], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - [Interlaken - Kurgarten, Woman by fountain in front of a mountain in the Swiss Alps], 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - [Interlaken. Blumenuhr, The Flower Clock, in Kurgarten], 8
    - Verso: Interlaken. Blumenuhr [The Flower Clock] im Kurgarten. [Spa Gardens], 8-verso
    - Interlaken, [town at the base of the the Bernese Alps], 9
    - Verso: Interlaken, 9-verso
    - Oberer Gletscher [Upper Glacier], Grindelwald; [house at the base of a glacier in the Bernese Alps], 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - Zurich und die Alpen [Zurich and the Alps]. Glarnisch 2910m, Bachistock 2920m, Hausstock 3156m, Boser Faulen 2804m, Pfannenstock 2572m, Drusberg 2281m, Bifertenstock 3486m, Todi 3623m, Claride 3270m, 11
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 11-verso
    - Luzern, Lowendenkmal; Helvetiorum Fidei ac Virtuti [The Lion Monument: Swiss faith and courage], 12
    - Verso: Luzern, Lowendenkmal[The Lion Monument]; Lyon of Lucerne, 12-verso
    - Luzern und Pilatus, [Mount Pilatus], 13
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 13-verso
    - Luzern. Lowendenkmal [The Lion Monument], 14
    - Verso: Luzern. Lowendenkmal [The Lion Monument], 14-verso
    - [Luzern. Lowendenkmal, The Lion Monument], 15
    - Verso: Luzern. Lowendenkmal [The Lion Monument], 15-verso
    - Luzern. Seebrucke, Banhof und die Alpen [Pier, train station, and the Alps], 16
    - Verso: Luzern. Seebrucke, Banhof und die Alpen [Pier, train station, and the Alps], 16-verso
  - United States of America (Alaska), circa 1915 - 1916; 5 (Box 1601)
    - Skagway Alaska; This is the top of "A.B" mountain where that other picture of me was taken., 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Totem pole in Wrangell, Alaska], 2
    - Verso: A totem pole, Wrangell, Alaska., 2-verso
    - Skagway, Alaska, Sunday School, June 18, 1916, 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - Resurrection Bay, Alaska.1913, 4
    - Verso: "The permanent snow fields of Alaska are only around mighty mountain ranges.", 4-verso
    - [A moose in the water in Alaska], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - [Bear pulling a sled in Alaska], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - Walrus asleep on the ice in Bering Sea, 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - Sulphur Botton Whale; P. Coffman U.S. Whaling Co. Alaska, 8
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 8-verso
    - [Fin back whale on dock. P. Coffman U.S. Whaling Co. Alaska, 9
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 9-verso
    - [?] Eskimo Women in Alaska], 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - [Man standing with dogs in Alaska], 11
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 11-verso
  - United States of America (California), undated; 6 (Box 1601)
    - [California coast Redwoods], 1
    - Verso: CALIFORNIA COAST REDWOODS. These towering 2,000-year-old forest giants are among the remaining few groves of unprotected virgin Redwoods adjacent to Redwood state parks, needing protection. Your contributions are urgently needed. Save-the-Redwoods League, 114 Sansome Street, San Francisco, California. Photo by Howard King and Doug Yule, 1-verso
    - General Geo. A Custer; Curley, one of Custer's Trusted Crow Indian scouts. Custer's tragic battlefield where on June 25th, 1876 the gallant Major General and his little band of men were overwhelmed and killed by warriors of the Sioux and Cheyenne tribes - Near Crow Agency Monanta on the Burlington Line via Yellowstone and Glacier National Parks to the Pacific Northwest., 2
    - Verso: 7.50 car & tunnel, 1.70 gas, 2.00 dinner, .50 breakfast mine, 2.50 garage Atlantic City, 2 gas, 1.20 ferry Wilington, 2-verso
    - Garden Court, Palace Hotel, San Francisco, 3
    - Verso: The famed GARDEN COURT of the Palace Hotel - traditional gathering place of San Francisco's society and visiting celebrities., 3-verso
    - [San Francisco from top of The Mark], 4
    - Verso: SAN FRANCISCO FROM TOP OF THE MARK. This view seen from atop Knob Hill shows San Francisco's financial and business district, the San Francisco-Oakland Bay Bridge, Yerba Buena Island and the hills of Metropolitan Oakland in the distant background., 4-verso
    - [Yosemite Falls, California], 5
    - Verso: YOSEMITE FALLS YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK, CALIFORNIA. Nowhere else in the world may be seen a waterfall spectacle such as is found in Yosemite National Park. The Upper Yosemite Fall drops 1,430 feet in one sheer fall, a height equal to about nine Niagara Falls. The lower Yosemite Fall, immediately below, has a drop of 320 feet, or two Niagaras more. Counting the series of cascades in between, the total drop from the crest of the upper fall to the base of the lower fall is 2,425 feet., 5-verso
    - Crystal Plunge of the Ambassador Lido..Los Angeles, 6
    - Verso: LOS ANGELES AMBASSADOR. The Crystal Plunge Offers endless opportunity for healthful recreation-swimming, sun-tanning and a complete "Health Spa" rendering baths, massage and conditioning all the year 'round., 6-verso
  - United States of America (Colorado), undated; 7 (Box 1601)
    - "Colorado, Playground of America" -President Theodore Roosevelt. The new Colorado state flag. Originated by Denver chapter, Daughters of the American Revolution. Adopted by the eighteenth general assemby, May 6, 1911. Bill introduced by senator W.H. Sharpley. Design by A.C. Carson, President Ohio Society of Colorado., 1
    - Verso: Colorado state flag-significaions: Letter "C" Capital for Colorado, Centennial State, Columbine State, Red Color-"Colorado" in Spanish. Gold Greatest gold state. All-the-year sunshine, one Columnine color, one color more than the U.S. flag. White...Greatest silver state, eternal mountain snow, one Columbine color. Yale blue...All-the-year blue sky, one Columbine color, (Color of the D.A.R.). Cords and tassles...Two cords of gold and silver, strands intertwined, one gold and one silver tassle., 1-verso
    - [The Golden Bee English Pub, Colorado], 2
    - Verso: THE GOLDEN BEE, and authentic English Pub of the 1800 era located in the International Center of the famous Broadmoor resort hotel in Colorado Springs, Colorado. "My Work shop will Mar. [March] 6th. We sure are "buzzing" Haha. Junean Hatter [?], 2-verso
    - Gem Lake, Estes Park, Colo. [Colorado], 3
    - Verso: View of Estes Park and Rocky Mountain National Park. Playground of the World., 3-verso
    - [The Brown Palace Hotel], 4
    - Verso: The Brown Palace Hotel. Denver, Colorado. 600 completely air conditioned rooms., 4-verso
    - Panorama of the Horseshoe Park and the Mummy Range, Estes Park; Rocky Mountain National Park, Colo. [Colorado], 5
    - Verso: The Mummy Range is one of the most prominent features of the Rocky Mountain National Park and dominate its northwestern section. Horseshoe Park is a tremendous upland valley, hemmed in by giant hills, the haunt of the deer and Bighorn sheep, thru which Fall River flows. "Daniel Ue" [?], 5-verso
    - Mt. Ypsilon from High Drive. Estes Park; Rocky Mountain National Park, Colorado., 6
    - Verso: Mt. Ypsilon is one of the most noted peaks in the Rocky Mountain National Park, easily distinguished from its fellow mountains in the Mummy Range by its distinctive face resembling the Greek letter "Y" from which it revieves its name., 6-verso
    - Luxuriant growths of brilliant hued wild flowers add a distinct charm. Rocky Mountain National--Estes Park, Colorado. Burlington Route--Direct to the Park., 7
    - Verso: Bulrington Route. The National Park Lane., 7-verso
    - Grand Lake, Colorado. One of the most beautiful lakes in the world--Elevation 8,400 feet on grand circle tour from Denver, through Rocky Mountain National--Estes Park. Burlington Route--Direct to the Park., 8
    - Verso: Burlington Route. Never disappoints to Colorado points., 8-verso
    - [Brown Palace Hotel lobby], 9
    - Verso: Unique lobby of the famous Brown Palace Hotel. Denver, Colorado. Here is real hospitality and excellent food. Where the world registers., 9-verso
    - MANASSA MAULER MUSEUM; Birthplace of William Harrison "Jack" Dempsey, King of the World Heavy-weight Boxing Champtions, 1919-1926. The most popular living person in the World of Sports today., 10
    - Verso: MANASSA, COLORADO. Conejos County. Beautiful-Thriving-Farming Community. Was first settled in 1879, by Mormon Colonists who chose the name after the eldest son of Joseph of Ancient Israel. Incorporated 1889-Popularion 878-Altitude 7683.], 10-verso
    - [Victor, Colorado sign], 11
    - Verso: Victor, Colorado, 11-verso
    - Fort Greene Ville (Greeneville, Ohio), 12
    - Verso: FORT GREENE-VILLE 1793-1796. Headquarters of Gen. Anthony Wayne in his campaign against the Confederated Indian Tribes, it was the largest log block house fort erected by his army, in the Northwest Territory. It covered about 50 acres. Here Gen. Wayne negotiated the famous "Treaty of Greene-Ville", which was signed Aug. 3 1795. Greenville, Ohio., 12-verso
    - Victor, Colorado. City of Gold Mines. [Sign], 13
    - Verso: CRIPPLE CREEK COLO. "The World's Greatest Gold Camp", and VICTOR COLO.,"The City of Mines" are in the center of the world's most renowned gold-producting district, nearly two miles above sea level. Total production $600,000,000., 13-verso
    - Lowell Thomas Boyhood-Home Museum, 14
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas' boyhood home in Victor, Colorado., 14-verso
    - Front Cover of booklet that includes postcards 16-23, 15
    - Yonder is Cripple Creek, World's greatest gold camp. [Man with donkey], 16
    - Verso: THE PROSPECTOR AND HIS FAITHFUL BURRO symbol of gold mining. The sign stands at the junction of the road to Cripple Creek, Colorado with Hwy. 24 at Divide, Colorado. It speaks eloquesntly in directing the vacation traveler., 16-verso
    - [Cripple Creek], 17
    - Verso: "THE GLORY THAT WAS ONCE CRIPPLE CREEK" as seen through one of the hundreds of abandoned gallows frames which mark the sites of producers of the past. Mt. Pisgah and the Main Range in the background., 17-verso
    - [Gold King and Molly Kathleen mines], 18